Federal Music Project Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
George Allen Foster was appointed acting deputy director of the National Office after the resignation of the national director, Nikolai Sokoloff. This was after the Federal Project No. 1 was terminated on June 30, 1939 and before the WPA Music Program began in August 1939. When a permanent director was appointed, Mr. Foster returned to his duties as regional supervisor for Region I (New York State and New England). The correspondence in this collection spans 1936 to 1948 and covers salary issues and job responsibilities during the agency’s life and, afterwards, during his tenure as manager of the New Orleans Symphony Society. The photographs feature directors and supervisors of various programs including Nikolai Sokoloff and Harry L. Hopkins (WPA Director), conferences of Music Supervisors of the Professional and Services Division Directors and the National Advisory Committee, and of Mr. Foster himself. One photograph shows Eleanor Roosevelt in the inaugural broadcast of This Work Pays Your Community Week or See For Yourself. Another photograph depicts the WPA Tipica Orchestra in San Antonio, Texas. Various reports are included in the collection, such as the 390-page “The Record of Program Operation and Accomplishment of the FMP and the WPA Music Program” which is the most comprehensive summary of the work of these organizations from 1935 to 1943. Two other significant reports are the “Check List of Historical Records Survey Publications” and the “Bibliographies of Research Projects Reports”, both from 1943.
Wilda M. Heiss, 1999
Organization of the Federal Music Project Collection
The Federal Music Project Collection is organized into nine series:
Reports, 1936-1943
Music Library, 1936-1941
Music and Other Performing Media, 1936-1940
Composers' Index, 1936-1941
Bio-Bibliographical Index of Musicians, 1936-1940
Writings, 1906
Programs, 1935-1943
Clippings, 1935-1941
George Allen Foster Collection, 1936-1948
http://lccn.loc.gov/2006560198
Container List
- Reports, 1936-1943 and undated (Box 1-9)
  - Exhibit Reports (Box 1-6)
    Exhibit Reports include compilations of state reports which consist of charts, lists, programs, reports, minutes, correspondence, manuals, bulletins, transcripts, catalogs, addresses, method and study books, and black and white photo prints.
    Arranged numerically.
    - Number 1-6, 8-9, (9 folders) (Box 1)
    - Number 10-12, (5 folders) (Box 2)
    - Number 13-21, (10 folders) (Box 3)
    - Number 22-25, (8 folders) (Box 4)
    - Number 26-31, 33-35, (10 folders) (Box 5)
    - Number 36-38, 40-41, (7 folders) (Box 6)
  - Special Reports (Box 7)
    Special Reports consist of reports, memoranda, and black and white photo prints.
    Arranged chronologically.
    - 1937, (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - 1940, (1 folder) (Box 7)
    - 1941, (1 folder) (Box 7)
    - 1942, (1 folder) (Box 7)
    - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - State Reports (Box 8-9)
    State Reports consist of reports, memoranda, black and white photographic prints, bulletins, lists, a journal, instruction manuals.
    Arranged alphabetically by state.
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - California, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Delaware, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Illinois, (4 folders) (Box 8)
    - Indiana, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Kansas, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Kentucky, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Michigan, (1 folder) (Box 8)
    - Minnesota, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - Missouri, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - New Jersey, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - New York, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - Ohio, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - Utah, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 9)
    - Wisconsin, (1 folder) (Box 9)
- Music Library, 1936-1941 and undated (Box 10-11 and 144-199)
  - Catalogs (Box 10-11)
    Catalogs consist of typescript lists of musical compositions by medium, arranged alphabetically by state, and lists of recordings and instrumentations, arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - State (Box 10-11)
      - California, (7 folders) (Box 10)
      - Colorado, (1 folder) (Box 10)
      - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 10)
      - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 10)
      - Massachusetts, (6 folders) (Box 10)
      - Michigan, (1 folder) (Box 10)
      - New York, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - Ohio, (6 folders) (Box 11)
      - Rhode Island, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - Texas, (1 folder) (Box 11)
      - Vermont, (1 folder) (Box 11)
      - Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 11)
      - Wyoming, (1 folder) (Box 11)
    - Subject (Box 11)
      - Catalogue of electrical transcriptions, (1 folder) (Box 11)
      - Instrumentation of compositions, (1 folder) (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 11)
  - Index Cards (Box 144-199)
    Index Cards are divided into four categories: Composer, State, Title and Type of Composition.
    Each category is arranged alphabetically, except for Type of Composition which is in quasi-alphabetical order.
    - Composer (Box 144-159)
      - Aa - Baro (Box 144)
      - Barr - Bol (Box 145)
      - Bon - Cho (Box 146)
      - Chr - D (Box 147)
      - Ea - Ger (Box 148)
      - Ges - Grof (Box 149)
      - Gros - Hop (Box 150)
      - Hor - Lak (Box 151)
      - Lal - Mars (Box 152)
      - Mart - Mozart (Box 153)
      - Mozart (cont.) - Rame (Box 154)
      - Rami - Ry (Box 155)
      - Sa - Sn (Box 156)
      - So - Ti (Box 157)
      - To - V (Box 158)
      - W - Z (Box 159)
    - State (Box 160-176)
      - Alabama - California (Box 160)
      - California (cont.) (Box 161-163)
      - California (cont.) - Illinois (Box 164)
      - Illinois (cont.) (Box 165)
      - Illinois (cont.) - Louisiana (Box 166)
      - Maine - Massachusetts (Box 167)
      - Michigan - Missouri (Box 168)
      - Missouri (cont.) - New Jersey (Box 169)
      - New Mexico - New York (Box 170)
      - New York (cont.) (Box 171)
      - New York (cont.) - North Carolina (Box 172)
      - North Carolina (cont.) - Ohio (Box 173)
      - Ohio (cont.) - Pennsylvania (Box 174)
      - Pennsylvania (cont.) - Texas (Box 175)
      - Texas (cont.) - Wyoming; Unidentified (Box 176)
    - Title (Box 177-182)
      - Set A (Box 177-178)
        - A-N (Box 177)
        - O-Z (Box 178)
      - Set B (Box 179-180)
        - A-N (Box 179)
        - O-Z (Box 180)
      - Set C (Box 181-182)
        - A-N (Box 181)
        - O-Z (Box 182)
    - Type of Composition (Box 183-199)
      - Americana - Band works (Box 183)
      - Band works (cont.) - Chamber music (Box 184)
      - Chamber music (cont.) - Choral (Box 185)
      - Choral (cont.) - Instrumental solos (Box 186)
      - Instrumental solos (cont.) - Marches (Box 187)
      - Symphonien - Forum-laboratory (Box 188)
      - Forum-laboratory (cont.) - Orchestral (Box 189)
      - Overtures - Premieres (Box 190)
      - Choral - Selections (Box 191)
      - Miscellaneous - Concert and radio orchestras and Small ensembles (Box 192)
      - Concert and radio orchestras and Small ensembles (cont.) - Symphonic and tone poems (Box 193)
      - Symphonic and tone poems (cont.) - Symphonies (Box 194)
      - Symphonies (cont.) - Vocal solos (Box 195)
      - Voice and orchestra - Forum-laboratory (Box 196)
      - Duplicates (Box 197-199)
- Music and Other Performing Media, 1936-1940 and undated (Box 12, 263-272)
  - Music (Box 263-264, 266-272)
    Music consists of photocopies of full scores and parts.
    Arranged alphabetically by composer.
    - Copland, Aaron (Box 263, 266)
      - El salón Mexico (Box 263, 266)
        - Photocopy of copyist's full score, bound, 2 copies; On t.p.: New York Public Library, 1937 (Box 263)
        - Photocopy of copyist's parts, 2 copies (Box 266)
    - Fuleihan, Anis (Box 263, 267-269)
      - Concerto for piano and string orchestra (Box 263, 267)
        - Photocopy of copyist's full score, bound, 2 copies; On t.p.: New York Public Library, 1937; At end: Composer's signature, June-July 1937 (Box 263)
        - Photocopy of copyist's parts, bound, 2 copies (Box 267)
      - Symphony (Box 263, 268-269)
        - Photocopy of copyist's full score, bound, 2 copies; On t.p.: New York Public Library, 1937; At end: Composer's signature, Oct. 1936 (Box 263)
        - Photocopy of copyist's parts, bound, 2 copies (Box 268-269)
    - Mason, Daniel Gregory (Box 264, 270-271)
      - A Lincoln symphony (Box 264, 270-271)
        - Photocopy of copyist's full score, bound, At top of p. 1: "Dedicated to the memory of Ossip Gabrilowitsch"; At end: New York, January 12, 1937 (Box 264)
        - Photocopy of copyist's parts, bound, 2 copies (Box 270-271)
    - Schultz, Esther, compiler (Box 12)
      - Canons, Rounds and Catches of 16, 17 and 18 Century (Box 12)
        - Typescript of music scores and text (Box 12)
    - Sedlaczek, Ludwig M. (Box 272)
      - Fanthasie [sic] no. 1 on Kentucky mountain songs (Box 272)
        - Manuscript full score in ink with pencil annotations (incomplete), On t.p.: Louisville, Ky. July 1936 (Box 272)
        - Negative photocopy of manuscript score (Box 272)
        - Manuscript parts (Box 272)
        - Negative photocopy of manuscript parts (Box 272)
  - Other Performing Media (Box 12, 265)
    Other Performing Media consists of manuscript scores, manuscript and photocopies of vocal parts, a typescript libretto and lyric sheets.
    - Alabama, (1 folder) (Box 12)
    - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 265)
    - Kentucky, (1 folder) (Box 265)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 12)
    - New York, (1 folder) (Box 12)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 265)
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 12)
- Composers' Index, 1936-1941 and undated (Box 13-23c, 200-231)
  - Composer (Box 13-21b)
    The Composer files consist of draft and final versions of typescript lists of musical compositions.
    - Draft (Box 13-21a)
      - A-Bl, (5 folders) (Box 13)
      - Bo-C, (7 folders) (Box 14)
      - D-F, (5 folders) (Box 15)
      - G-H, (7 folders) (Box 16)
      - I-L, (7 folders) (Box 17)
      - M-N, (5 folders) (Box 18)
      - O-R, (8 folders) (Box 19)
      - S, (9 folders) (Box 20)
      - T-Z, (8 folders) (Box 21a)
    - Final (Box 21b)
      - A-W, (21 folders) (Box 21b)
  - Index Cards (Box 200-231)
    The Index Cards are divided into three categories: Bio-pictures, Composers and Non-composers.
    Each category is arranged alphabetically by name.
    - Bio-pictures (Box 200)
      - A-Z (Box 200)
    - Composer (Box 201-231)
      - Ab-Bae (Box 201)
      - Bag-Ben (Box 202)
      - Ber-Boo (Box 203)
      - Bor-Br (Box 204)
      - Bu-Ca (Box 205)
      - Ce-Coo (Box 206)
      - Cop-Del (Box 207)
      - Dem-Ei (Box 208)
      - El-For (Box 209)
      - Fos-Ga (Box 210)
      - Ge-Gre (Box 211)
      - Gri-Hal (Box 212)
      - Ham-Hep (Box 213)
      - Her-Hol (Box 214)
      - Hom-Ji (Box 215)
      - Jo-Kn (Box 216)
      - Ko-La (Box 217)
      - Le-Lo (Box 218)
      - Lu-Mar (Box 219)
      - Mas-Mi (Box 220)
      - Mo-N (Box 221)
      - O-Pl (Box 222)
      - Po-Rh (Box 223)
      - Ri-Ro (Box 224)
      - Ru-Schl (Box 225)
      - Schm-Si (Box 226)
      - Sk-Sta (Box 227)
      - Ste-Thi (Box 228)
      - Tho-Va (Box 229)
      - Ve-Wh (Box 230)
      - Wi-Z (Box 231)
    - Non-composers (Box 200)
      - A-W (Box 200)
  - Questionnaires (Box 21c)
    The Questionnaire files consist of typescript and handwritten correspondence, indexes and lists of music compositions.
    Arranged alphabetically by state, then by composer.
    - California, (6 folders) (Box 21c)
    - Michigan, (1 folder) (Box 21c)
    - Correspondence, (1 folder) (Box 21c)
  - State (Box 22a-22b)
    The State files consist of typescript correspondence.
    - Alabama, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Arizona, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - California, (2 folders) (Box 22a)
    - Colorado, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Delaware, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Georgia, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Illinois, (2 folders) (Box 22a)
    - Indiana, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Kansas, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Kentucky, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Louisiana, (1 folder) (Box 22a)
    - Maine, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Maryland, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Massachusetts, (2 folders) (Box 22b)
    - Michigan, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Missouri, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - New Jersey, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
    - New York, (1 folder) (Box 22b)
  - Subject (Box 23a-23b)
    The Subject files consist of typescript correspondence, lists, reports, addresses, notes and press clippings.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Additions to index since March 1940, (1 folder) (Box 23a)
    - Addresses of composers, (2 folders) (Box 23a)
    - Composers: biographies, correspondence, lists, notes, (3 folders) (Box 23a)
    - Federal Theatre Project list of American music, (1 folder) (Box 23a)
    - Press releases and reviews and sample index, (1 folder) (Box 23a)
    - Replies to index letters, (1 folder) (Box 23a)
    - State breakdowns on composers, (2 folders) (Box 23b)
    - Various lists on composers, (4 folders) (Box 23b)
  - Type of Composition (Box 23c)
    The Type of Composition files consist of typescript lists of composers and their works; requests for catalogs; information from composers; miscellaneous incomplete records.
    Arranged alphabetically by type of composition, then by composer.
    - Cantatas, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Chamber music, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Chorus, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Chorus with orchestra, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Concerti, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Fantasies, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Instrumental solos, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Liturgical, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Marches, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Opera, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Overtures, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Pageants, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Rhapsodies, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Selections, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Solos with orchestra, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Suites, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Symphonic and tone poems, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Symphonies, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Various--Americana, Cantatas, Concerti, Sacred works, Symphonies, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Vocal solos, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Waltzes, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
    - Requests for catalogs and information from composers, (2 folders) (Box 23c)
    - Miscellaneous incomplete records, (1 folder) (Box 23c)
- Bio-Bibliographical Index of Musicians, 1936-1940 and undated (Box 24-33, 232-262)
  - Correspondence (Box 24)
    Correspondence consists of typescript and handwritten correspondence.
    Arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - 1937-40, (1 folder) (Box 24)
  - Index (Box 25)
    The Index files consist of typescript and handwritten bibliographies and lists of musicians.
    Arranged alphabetically by category.
    - Appendix, (1 folder) (Box 25)
    - Drafts, (4 folders) (Box 25)
    - Final, (1 folder) (Box 25)
    - Preface, (1 folder) (Box 25)
    - Uncorrected, (1 folder) (Box 25)
  - Index Cards (Box 232-262)
    The Index Cards are divided into five categories: Authors, Books, Books on Folk Music, Musicians and Processing.
    Each category is arranged alphabetically by name, title or subject.
    - Authors, 4 boxes (Box 232-235)
    - Books, 6 boxes (Box 236-241)
    - Books, folk music, 5 boxes (Box 242-246)
    - Musicians, 12 boxes (Box 247-258)
    - Processing, 4 boxes (Box 259-262)
  - Musicians (Box 26-33)
    The Musicians files consist of draft and omitted handwritten lists of musicians and their specialty.
    Arranged alphabetically by name.
    - Draft (Box 26-32)
      - A-Ber, (6 folders) (Box 26)
      - Bes-Che, (6 folders) (Box 27)
      - Chi-D, (7 folders) (Box 28)
      - E-Gog, (7 folders) (Box 29)
      - Gol-Siz, (6 folders) (Box 30)
      - Ske-U, (7 folders) (Box 31)
      - V-Z, (10 folders) (Box 32)
    - Omitted (Box 33)
      - A-C, W, (8 folders) (Box 33)
  - Subject (Box 24)
    The Subject files consist of typescript and handwritten memoranda, lectures, bibliographies, biographies of musicians, syllabi, newspaper clippings and various lists.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject or name.
    - Administrative records, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - America's prodigious musical life, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Dvořák, Antonín, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Evans, Luther H., Dr.: Music study guide is a monumental work, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Folk music, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Guide to the study of music in America, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Historical Records Survey, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Lists (Box 24)
      - Bibliography, (1 folder) (Box 24)
      - General, (1 folder) (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 24)
      - Periodicals, (1 folder) (Box 24)
      - Preliminary references, (1 folder) (Box 24)
      - References, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Paderewski, Ignace Jan, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Processing records, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Shapleigh, Bertram, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Subject index, (1 folder) (Box 24)
    - Syllabus, (1 folder) (Box 24)
- Writings, 1906 and undated (Box 34-35)
  Writings consist of typescript translations and a libretto.
  Arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Bücher, Karl. Work and Rhythm., Translated by the Reference and Research Department, Music Education Division, New York WPA Music Project. (Box 34)
  - Taneev (Taneyev), Sergei. Mobile Counterpoint., Translated by Julia Krenov. (Box 35)
  - Wolff, Herman E. The Tinder Box. (Box 34)
- Programs, 1935-1943 (Box 36-137)
  Printed, mimeographed and typescript programs.
  Arranged chronologically by year and then alphabetically by state.
  - 1935 (Box 36)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 36)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 36)
    - New Jersey, (1 folder) (Box 36)
    - New York, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Ohio, (1 folder) (Box 36)
    - Pennsylvania, (1 folder) (Box 36)
  - 1936 (Box 37-49)
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 37)
    - Arizona, (1 folder) (Box 37)
    - California, (8 folders) (Box 37)
    - California (cont.), (15 folders) (Box 38-39)
    - Colorado, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Connecticut, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Delaware, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Florida, (4 folders) (Box 40)
    - Illinois, (13 folders) (Box 40)
    - Indiana, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Kentucky, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Louisiana, (1 folder) (Box 40)
    - Maine, (12 folders) (Box 41)
    - Maryland, (1 folder) (Box 41)
    - Massachusetts, (7 folders) (Box 41)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (17 folders) (Box 42)
    - Michigan, (1 folder) (Box 42)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 43)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 43)
    - Missouri, (1 folder) (Box 43)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 43)
    - New Hampshire, (1 folder) (Box 43)
    - New Jersey, (9 folders) (Box 43)
    - New Jersey (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 44)
    - New York, (9 folders) (Box 44)
    - New York (cont.), (13 folders) (Box 45)
    - North Carolina, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Ohio, (12 folders) (Box 46)
    - Ohio (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 47)
    - Oklahoma, (3 folders) (Box 47)
    - Oregon, (3 folders) (Box 47)
    - Pennsylvania, (4 folders) (Box 47)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (17 folders) (Box 48)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (4 folders) (Box 49)
    - Rhode Island, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - South Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - Tennessee, (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - Texas, (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - Utah, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Vermont, (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - Virginia, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Washington, (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - West Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - Wisconsin, (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - 1937 (Box 50-66)
    - Alabama, (1 folder) (Box 50)
    - Arizona, (1 folder) (Box 50)
    - Arkansas, (1 folder) (Box 50)
    - California, (8 folders) (Box 50)
    - California (cont.), (18 folders) (Box 51-53)
    - California (cont.), (1 folder) (Box 54)
    - Colorado, (12 folders) (Box 54)
    - Connecticut, (13 folders) (Box 54)
    - Delaware, (3 folders) (Box 54)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 55)
    - Florida, (12 folders) (Box 55)
    - Georgia, (1 folder) (Box 55)
    - Illinois, (12 folders) (Box 55)
    - Indiana, (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 56)
    - Louisiana, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Maine, (13 folders) (Box 56)
    - Massachusetts, (9 folders) (Box 56)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (17 folders) (Box 57)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Michigan, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Minnesota, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 58)
    - Missouri, (11 folders) (Box 58)
    - Nebraska, (1 folder) (Box 58)
    - New Hampshire, (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - New Jersey, (13 folders) (Box 59)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 59)
    - New York, (15 folders) (Box 59)
    - New York (cont.), (17 folders) (Box 60)
    - New York (cont.), (9 folders) (Box 61)
    - North Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 61)
    - Ohio, (6 folders) (Box 61)
    - Ohio (cont.), (10 folders) (Box 62)
    - Ohio (cont.), (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Oklahoma, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Oregon, (1 folder) (Box 63)
    - Pennsylvania, (9 folders) (Box 63)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (21 folders) (Box 64-65)
    - Rhode Island, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - South Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - Tennessee, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - Texas, (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - Utah, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - Vermont, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - West Virginia, (1 folder) (Box 66)
    - Wisconsin, (1 folder) (Box 66)
  - 1938 (Box 67-91)
    - Alabama, (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Arizona, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - Arkansas, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - California, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - California (cont.), (37 folders) (Box 68-72)
    - California (cont.), (5 folders) (Box 73)
    - Colorado, (12 folders) (Box 73)
    - Connecticut, (4 folders) (Box 73)
    - Connecticut (cont.), (11 folders) (Box 74)
    - Delaware, (13 folders) (Box 74)
    - District of Columbia, (1 folder) (Box 75)
    - Florida, (1 folder) (Box 75)
    - Georgia, (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Illinois, (13 folders) (Box 75)
    - Indiana, (3 folders) (Box 75)
    - Iowa, (1 folder) (Box 76)
    - Kansas, (1 folder) (Box 76)
    - Louisiana, (3 folders) (Box 76)
    - Maine, (13 folders) (Box 76)
    - Maryland, (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - Massachusetts, (3 folders) (Box 76)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (9 folders) (Box 77)
    - Massachusetts (cont.), (3 folders) (Box 78)
    - Michigan, (9 folders) (Box 78)
    - Michigan, (4 folders) (Box 79)
    - Minnesota, (1 folder) (Box 79)
    - Mississippi, (1 folder) (Box 79)
    - Missouri, (6 folders) (Box 79)
    - Missouri (cont.), (7 folders) (Box 80)
    - Nebraska, (3 folders) (Box 80)
    - New Hampshire, (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - New Jersey, (13 folders) (Box 80)
    - New Mexico, (1 folder) (Box 80)
    - New York, (24 folders) (Box 81-82)
    - New York (cont.), (7 folders) (Box 83)
    - North Carolina, (1 folder) (Box 83)
    - Ohio, (2 folders) (Box 83)
    - Ohio (cont.), (18 folders) (Box 84-85)
    - Ohio (cont.), (6 folders) (Box 86)
    - Oklahoma, (2 folders) (Box 86)
    - Oregon, (2 folders) (Box 86)
    - Pennsylvania, (2 folders) (Box 86)
    - Pennsylvania (cont.), (26 folders) (Box 87-89)